Company Benefits Summary Plan Description /4060
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Southern Bell, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Southern Farm Bureau Life Insurance Co., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Southern Natural Resources, Inc., 1964-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Southland Paper Mills Inc., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Southwest Denver Community Mental Health Services, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Southwestern Public Service Company, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Stag, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Standard Unit Parts Corporation (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Standard Products Company, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- State Savings & Loan Association (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Stern, Melvin J. M.D. P.A. (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Sterling Stamping Company, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Stewarts Food Basket, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Doctors Stevens & Marshall (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Sunbeam Appliance Service Company, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Sy's Drugstore, Inc., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- T.R.B. Enterprises, Inc., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Tampa Electric Company, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Teague Industries, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Teamsters Local No. 710, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Teepak, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Thomas Electric, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Timex Corporation, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Toots Willen Construction Co. Inc. (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Trane Thermal Company, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Transue & Williams Steel Forging, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Travelers Corporation (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Tucker, Royal D., M.D., Inc. (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Tustison, Winston A. M.D., Inc., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Union Carbide (Box 10, Folder 1)
- United States Independent Telephone Association, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Ullman and Emanuel, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- United Centrifugal Pumps, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- United States Pipe and Foundry Co., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- United Virginia Bankshares Inc., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Vaillancourt, R.A., P.A., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Valley Gas Company, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Valley Urological Association, Inc., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Valveland, Inc., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Vanguard Group, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Van Orden, Richard T. M.D. (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Van Sickle Industries, Inc., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Veeder Industries Inc., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Walters Bank and Trust, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Ward Aluminum Products, Inc., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Weber, W.F., M.D., Inc. (Box 10, Folder 17)
- West Coast Lumber Inspection Bureau, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Western Bancorporation and its Affiliates, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Western Door and Sash Company, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Western Gillette, Inc., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Western Pennsylvania Hospital, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Weyerhaeuser Company, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Weyerhaeuser Company, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Weyerhaeuser Company, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Whaley, Chapman, and Hannah, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Whirlpool Corporation, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- White, C.C., Jr. M.D. Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- White's Concrete Products Inc., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Wingert, C.H. Jr. M.D., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Wolverine World Wide Inc., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Worcester At Museum, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Wright, W.E., Co., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Wyman- Gordon Co., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Yasuyuki Fukushima, M.D. (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Zimmerman Equipment Company, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Zinsco Electrical Products, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Qualified Pension Plans of 50 Large Industrial Companies, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. Benefit Plans under the 1978 Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Bankers Trust Co., 1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Top 50 Management Overview and Survey Report, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- American National Insurance Company, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Consolidated Edison Company Inc., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Bangor Publishing Company: Pension Plan, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- General Retirement System of Jefferson County, Alabama, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- UAW: Ford, Bendix, Caterpillar Pension Plans, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- General Motors Corp., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- First Commercial Banks Inc., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Teamster Pension Plan of Philadelphia (Box 11, Folder 13)
- International Typographical Union, 1972-1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- The Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- The Bendix Corporation, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Building Service Employees Retirement and Pension Fund, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- The Boeing Company, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Boeing Employee Retirement Plan, 1966-1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Chase Manhattan Bank, N.A., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Chase Manhattan Employees' Benefit Program, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. Benefit Plans, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Caterpillar Tractor Company, 1967-1977 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Ford Motor Company, 1967-1982 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation, 1968-1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Freight Drivers and Helpers, 1964-1983 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- General Motors Corporation, 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- General Motors Corporation, 1961-1976 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Gulf Oil Corporation, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Martin Marietta Corporation, 1963-1982 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Westinghouse (Box 11, Folder 32)
- J. I. Case Company, 1958-1980 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Southern California Lumber Industry, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Bakery and Confectionary Industry (Box 11, Folder 35)